YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 1. General and History
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VII. WORLD'S YWCA REFERENCE FILES
  - Annual Reports (incomplete)
    - 1974-2001 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Committee to Nominate American Members of the World's Council, 1933-46 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Conferences
    - 1st-4th, 1898- (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - 5th, 1914 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Budapest, 1928 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1937-39, 1960-65 (Box 67, Folder 6-9)
    - North America Area Conference of the YWCA: proceedings, 1937 (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
    - Canada-United States Conference of the YWCA: proceedings, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 4-7)
  - Consultations, 1955-59, 1961-1962, 1966, 1970-74 (Box 68, Folder 8-11)
  - Council: proceedings/reports
    - 1938, 1947, 1951, 1955, 1959, 1979, 1983, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 1-10)
    - 1991, 1995, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
  - Programmes and Projects
    - Cooperation for Development, 1977-86 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Health Cluster Project, 1983-84 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - International Training Institute, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - International Voluntary Service, circa 1964 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Mutual Service, 1951-59 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Prayer Circle, 1935-51 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Refugee and Rehabilitation Services, 1948-86 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - World YWCA Membership Day, 1961-72 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - World YWCA Day
      - 1965-72 (Box 70, Folder 11-12)
      - 1980-94 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - YMCA-YWCA Week of Prayer, 1914, 1935-2000 (Box 71, Folder 2-6)
  - Publications
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1933-69 (Box 71, Folder 7-10)
      - 1972-91, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
    - Common Concern (incomplete)
      - 1976-93 (Box 72, Folder 3-10)
      - 1994-2001 (Box 73, Folder 1-4)
    - Directories, 1939-97, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 5-7)
    - Human Rights, 1949, 1984-87 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Pack [of Addresses] for Europe, 1949, 1981, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Perspective, 1975-76 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Prayers and Prayer Calendars, 1901-16, 1960-81, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 2-3)
    - Programme Bulletin and Programme Paper, 1961-73 (Box 74, Folder 4-7)
    - Religion
      - 1942-65 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - 1970s-86, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Women's International Quarterly
      - Oct 1912-Jul 1916 (Box 75, Folder 2-3)
      - Oct 1916-Jul 1919 (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
    - World's YWCA Monthly (incomplete), 1941-67 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - World's YWCA News Service, 1923-30 (Box 76, Folder 4-5)
    - World's YWCA Quarterly, 1896-Jul 1912 (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
    - Young Women on the Move, 1994-97 (Box 77, Folder 4)